Lesson 12, Bob's big cookie order.
The family is gathered around the dinner table.
Bob tells them about his deal with the village market.
He asks his kids for help baking the cookies.
I know I've been down to the dumps since I got fired, but things are looking up now.
The village market wants to sell our cookies.
That's great news, Dad.
But we're going to have to bake like crazy over the weekend.
They want 2,000 cookies by Monday.
2,000 cookies in three days?
Don't you think you've bitten off more than you can chew?
Yeah, you're going to be running around like a chicken with its head cut off.
Fortunately, there are four of us here.
You kids will have to pitch in too.
Sorry, but I can't.
I have to finish Ted's chemistry homework.
Then I've got to get going on my election speech.
What's that about doing Ted's chemistry homework?
Never mind.
Amber will help out with the cookies instead of Nicole.
For heaven's sake, Nicole, it's like pulling teeth getting you to do any work around here.